<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Solutions on StellerCore Technology (Shenzhen) Co., Ltd.</title><link>https://axel888666.github.io/starcore/en/solutions/</link><description>Recent content in Solutions on StellerCore Technology (Shenzhen) Co., Ltd.</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://axel888666.github.io/starcore/en/solutions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Automotive Industry Solutions</title><link>https://axel888666.github.io/starcore/en/solutions/automotive/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://axel888666.github.io/starcore/en/solutions/automotive/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Through big data technology, we collect and analyze various data from automotive manufacturing processes in real-time, enabling real-time tracking and analysis of production conditions to improve production efficiency, product quality, and reduce manufacturing costs.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Banking Industry Solutions</title><link>https://axel888666.github.io/starcore/en/solutions/banking/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://axel888666.github.io/starcore/en/solutions/banking/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;StellerCore Technology provides comprehensive big data platform solutions for the banking industry, helping banks achieve digital transformation, enhance risk management capabilities and customer service levels. Build financial-grade big data platforms based on Apache Hadoop ecosystem, supporting massive data processing and real-time analysis.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Insurance Industry Solutions</title><link>https://axel888666.github.io/starcore/en/solutions/insurance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://axel888666.github.io/starcore/en/solutions/insurance/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Provide comprehensive big data solutions for the insurance industry, covering core business scenarios such as actuarial modeling, risk assessment, anti-fraud, and customer service, helping insurance companies achieve digital transformation and intelligent operations.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Energy Industry Solutions</title><link>https://axel888666.github.io/starcore/en/solutions/energy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://axel888666.github.io/starcore/en/solutions/energy/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Provide complete solutions for data collection, storage, and analysis for energy enterprises such as power, oil, and natural gas, helping energy companies achieve intelligent operations and digital transformation.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Telecommunications Industry Solutions</title><link>https://axel888666.github.io/starcore/en/solutions/telecommunications/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://axel888666.github.io/starcore/en/solutions/telecommunications/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Help telecommunications operators build big data platforms, support applications such as network optimization, customer service, and business analysis, improving network quality and customer experience.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Aerospace Solutions</title><link>https://axel888666.github.io/starcore/en/solutions/aerospace/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://axel888666.github.io/starcore/en/solutions/aerospace/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Provide high-reliability big data solutions for aerospace enterprises, supporting critical applications such as flight data analysis, equipment monitoring, and mission planning, ensuring successful execution of aerospace missions.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Smart City Solutions</title><link>https://axel888666.github.io/starcore/en/solutions/smart-city/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://axel888666.github.io/starcore/en/solutions/smart-city/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Provide smart city big data platforms for government and urban management departments, supporting applications such as urban governance, traffic management, and environmental monitoring, promoting intelligent urban development.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>